X in the insurance under the insurance
awards category is for outstanding
digital CX transformation in insurance.
Please put your hands together for FWD
group and welcome its head of
application delivery Mr. Sam Mohamad.
[Music]
[Applause]
Right. Good evening everyone and thanks
to Digital Banker for this award. It's
an honor to collect this on behalf of
FWD. Uh it highlights FWD's vision which
is changing the way people feel about
inference and our flagship super app
which is Omni. We through that we are
changing the way which our customers
interact with us. Thanks to a fantastic
team across the region who made this
happen. Thanks everyone. Have a great
night. Thank you. Congratulations once